<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Chicago Bar Foundation</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_newactivity2">Disabled / Deafblind</string>
    <string name="title_item_list">Areas of Law</string>
    <string name="title_item_detail">Organizations and Lawyers</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">Organizations and Lawyers</string>
    <string name="MainDescr">Chicago Bar Foundation and Motorola Mobility are working together to help connect people to free or low cost legal assistance in and around Chicago.</string>
    <string name="MainDescr2">Click on the <b>"FIND HELP"</b> button above to see a list of legal assistance available to you by specialty.</string>
    <string name="MainInst">MainInstr</string>
    <string name="desfstr">Speech-Disabled or Deafblind? CLICK HERE:</string>
    <string name="spnstreng">If you speak Spanish, CLICK HERE:</string>
    <string name="spnstr">Si usted habla español, haga CLIC AQUI:</string>
    <string name="contactstr">Contact us:  The Chicago Bar Foundation - 321 S Plymouth Ct, Ste 3B, Chicago, IL 60604, 312.554.1204</string>
    <string name="deafblind">If you are deaf, hard-of hearing, speech-disabled or deaf-blind....</string>
    <string name="trsservice">You may contact the organizations listed in here through Telecommunication Relay Service (TRS). \n \nThis is a free operator assistance service that allows you to place calls from a TTY to a standard voice telephone . \n \nTo place a TRS call from a standard voice phone to someone who uses a TTY, dial 711 to be automatically connected to a TRS operator.</string>
    <string name="before_search">If you have a legal problem and can’t pay for a lawyer, do one or all of the following:</string>
    <string name="before_search2">Call <u>CARPLS</u>, the Cook County Legal Aid Hotline at 312-738-9200 (if you are in Cook County)</string>
    <string name="before_search3">Visit www.IllinoisLegalAid.org for free legal information and helpful form</string>
    <string name="before_search4">Contact one of the legal aid organizations identified here. Scroll through the list to find the area of law you need, then click on the name to see a list of organizations that may be able to help you in that area.</string>
    <string name="after_search">Many more people need free legal help than the legal aid organizations can provide. Please be patient as you try to reach the organizations to find out if they can help you.</string>
    <string name="ifspanisheng">If you are Spanish speaking...</string>
    <string name="ifspanish">Si usted es de habla española ...</string>
    <string name="detailsspanisheng">You can call CARPLS at 312.738.9200 or go online to www.AyudaLegallL.org </string>
    <string name="detailsspanish">Usted puede llamar al CARPLS 312.738.9200 o visite el sitio www.AyudaLegallL.org </string>
    <string name="carpls_1">The best way to find out if you qualify for or can receive free legal help in or around Chicago is  to call CARPLS at 312-738-9200.</string>
    <string name="carpls_2">You can get legal advice and instructions from the CARPLS hotline. CARPLS also may try to refer you to another legal aid program for further assistance.</string>
    <string name="carpls_3">The hotline gets many more calls than CARPLS can answer. Please be patient, it may take up to 20 minutes to speak with an attorney. During heavy call times, you will also have the option to leave a message so that CARPLS can call you back.</string>
    <string name="ilao_1">www.IllinoisLegalAid.org provides free legal information, helpful forms and other resources. The website will help you learn about your legal problem and how court works.</string>
    <string name="ilao_2">If you are unable to find a lawyer to help you or need to handle your legal problem on your own, www.IllinoisLegalAid.org can help you create forms and give you instructions about representing yourself.</string>
    <string name="carpls_head"><u><b>CARPLS:</b></u></string>
    <string name="ilao_head"><u><b>Illinois Legal Aid:</b></u></string>
    <string name="info">ATTENTION: READ CAREFULLY BEFORE YOU USE A MOTOROLA FOUNDATION EXPERIENCE. LEGAL NOTICE: BY USING A MOTOROLA FOUNDATION EXPERIENCE (AS DEFINED BELOW), YOU AGREE THAT: YOU HAVE READ AND AGREED TO ALL THE TERMS OF THIS AGREEMENT, YOU ARE A PARTY TO AND CONSENT TO BE BOUND BY THIS AGREEMENT, YOU AGREE TO ALL THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS CONTAINED IN THIS AGREEMENT WITHOUT MODIFICATION. These terms and conditions apply to your Motorola products like mobile phones, tablets, and other mobile devices as well as applications, software, and services developed by Motorola Mobility Foundation ("Foundation" "we" or "us"), and downloaded from an app store, installed onto your computer, or pre-loaded onto a mobile device (collectively, "Motorola Foundation Experiences"). These terms and conditions, along with the Motorola Foundation Experiences privacy policy, form the entire legal agreement between you and Foundation, governing your use of the Motorola Foundation Experiences. Your use of the Motorola Foundation Experiences constitutes your consent to all of the terms of this agreement. 1. Ownership and License. As between you and Foundation, you own: Physical products that you have purchased, like smartphones, tablets, and other mobile devices. Any other hardware that you use to access and use the Motorola Foundation Experiences. User-generated content like photos, music, videos, and third-party applications you may install on your personal devices. As between you and Foundation, we own: Applications, software, and services that we have developed and made available for your use. Websites you may use to access certain Motorola Foundation Experiences and all content published on them. The name "Motorola Mobility Foundation" and any other logos, names, and other marks used to identify the Motorola Foundation Experiences. The Motorola Foundation Experiences are protected by United States and international laws and treaties protecting patents, trademarks, copyrights, and other intellectual property. Subject to applicable laws and the rights granted to you under this agreement, the Motorola Foundation Experiences consist of Foundation’s proprietary information. This agreement gives you no rights other than those stated in its terms. Your license will automatically terminate if you use the Motorola Foundation Experiences in any manner that violates this agreement, any applicable law, or any rights of Foundation or its licensors. We reserve the right to use any lawful means to prevent unauthorized use of the Motorola Foundation Experiences, such as technological barriers, IP mapping, and contacting your Internet Service Provider or wireless carrier. Except as described in this agreement you do not own the Motorola Foundation Experiences, but only have a limited, non-exclusive, revocable license to use the Motorola Foundation experiences as permitted by this agreement. The U.S. Government acknowledges Foundation’s representation that the Motorola Foundation Experiences and its documentation were developed at private expense and no part of them is in the public domain and that the software components of the Motorola Foundation Experiences are Restricted Computer Software as the term is defined in Clause 52.227-19(FAR) and is Commercial Computer Software as that term is defined in Subpart 227-471 (DFARS). Where applicable, use, duplication or disclosure by the U.S. Government is subject to restrictions as set forth in subparagraph (c)(1)(ii) of the Rights of Technical Data and Computer Software clause as DFARS 252.227-7013. Contractor/manufacturer is Motorola Mobility Foundation, 222 W. Merchandise Mart Plaza, Chicago, IL 60654. 2. Changes to Motorola Foundation Experiences. We may update, modify, enhance, suspend, or discontinue Motorola Foundation Experiences at any time including, without limitation, automatically delivering new versions or features to your Foundation products, applications, software and services when they become available. 3. Permitted and Prohibited Uses. You may use Motorola Foundation Experiences provided to you under license solely as provided to you and without modification. You may not use the Motorola Foundation Experiences provided to you under license: In any way that violates any applicable law. To create any information that contains computer viruses or any other computer code, files or programs designed to destroy, interrupt or otherwise limit the functionality of any computer software, computer hardware or other equipment. In a manner that could damage, disable, overburden, disrupt or impair the service or any Motorola Mobility LLC or Foundation owned network or system. To interfere with anyone else\'s ability to lawfully access and use the Motorola Foundation Experiences. To access any communications, content, or other information to which you do not have rights. To install, copy, modify, or distribute the Motorola Foundation Experiences (electronically or otherwise) on your computers or mobile devices, or make any copies, adaptations, derivative works, transcriptions, or merge any portion thereof, except as installed by their automated installation functions. To decompile, disassemble, de-crypt, reverse engineer, translate, or otherwise attempt to derive the source code of the Motorola Foundation Experiences or otherwise alter the Motorola Foundation Experiences. Use the Motorola Foundation Experiences to provide services to third parties. Transfer or resell any of the rights granted to you by these Terms of Use, except that you may authorize a third party for whom you are a legal guardian to use the Motorola Foundation Experiences, provided that you agree to remain legally responsible for that third party\'s use. 4. Responsibility for Use. You are responsible for your own use of the Motorola Foundation Experiences and all information that you associate with them. We expressly disclaim all responsibility for and all warranties (express or implied) related to the accuracy, completeness, safety, reliability, or lawfulness of information provided by the Motorola Foundation Experiences. By using the Motorola Foundation Experiences, you acknowledge that your use of the Motorola Foundation Experiences is at your own risk. 5. Eligibility: Your license to use the Motorola Foundation Experiences terminates automatically and retroactively if you are under the legal age of majority for your country of residence and do not have the permission of your parent or legal guardian to use the Motorola Foundation Experiences , or if your use of the the Motorola Foundation Experiences has previously been suspended or prohibited. BY DOWNLOADING, INSTALLING OR OTHERWISE USING ANY MOTOROLA FOUNDATION EXPERIENCES, YOU REPRESENT THAT YOU ARE OF LEGAL AGE OF MAJORITY IN YOUR COUNTRY OF RESIDENCE OR THAT YOU HAVE YOUR PARENT\'S OR LEGAL GUARDIAN\'S PERMISSION TO USE THE MOTOROLA FOUNDATION EXPERIENCES, AND HAVE NOT BEEN PREVIOUSLY SUSPENDED OR PROHIBITED FROM USING THE MOTOROLA FOUNDATION EXPERIENCES. 6. Disclaimer of Warranties and Limitations on Liability. TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW AND EXCEPT AS PROVIDED TO THE CONTRARY IN THIS AGREEMENT OR A SEPARATE WARRANTY AGREEMENT, WE PROVIDE THE MOTOROLA FOUNDATION EXPERIENCES "AS-IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND. WE ALSO DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES, WHETHER EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND, WHERE NOT EXPRESSLY STATED TO THE CONTRARY, NON-INFRINGEMENT. NO ORAL OR WRITTEN INFORMATION OR ADVICE GIVEN BY FOUNDATION, ITS EMPLOYEES, DISTRIBUTORS, DEALERS OR AGENTS SHALL INCREASE THE SCOPE OF THE ABOVE WARRANTIES OR CREATE ANY NEW WARRANTIES. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES, SO THE ABOVE EXCLUSION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IN THAT EVENT, ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES ARE LIMITED IN DURATION TO THE MINIMUM PERMITTED BY YOUR JURISDICTION. THIS WARRANTY GIVES YOU SPECIFIC LEGAL RIGHTS. YOU MAY HAVE OTHER RIGHTS, WHICH VARY FROM JURISDICTION TO JURISDICTION. YOUR USE OF THE MOTOROLA FOUNDATION EXPERIENCES DOES NOT, IN ANY WAY WHATSOEVER, EXTEND ANY OTHER WARRANTIES, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO ANY WARRANTIES THAT APPLY TO MOTOROLA PRODUCTS LIKE SMARTPHONES, TABLETS, OR OTHER MOBILE DEVICES. By using the Motorola Foundation Experiences, you agree that, to the extent permitted by law, we will have no liability for any special, indirect, or consequential damages that you may sustain from your use of the Motorola Foundation Experiences, whether due to loss of data or profits, negligence, or breach of contract. To the extent permitted by law, you assume all risks concerning the suitability and accuracy of the information that you send or receive using the Motorola Foundation Experiences. The Motorola Foundation Experiences may contain technical inaccuracies or typographical errors. We assume no responsibility for any such inaccuracies, errors, or omissions associated with the Motorola Foundation Experiences. The Motorola Foundation Experiences do not guarantee your safety. We make no claim that the Motorola Foundation Experiences will work effectively in case of an emergency. The Motorola Foundation Experiences are not a replacement for any current emergency, automated emergency or other emergency system, hardware or software. The Motorola Foundation Experiences are not fault-tolerant and are not designed, manufactured or intended for use in hazardous environments requiring fail-safe performance where a failure of the Motorola Foundation Experiences could lead directly to death, personal injury, or severe physical or environmental damage ("High Risk Activities"). You agree that we will not be responsible for any injury, environmental damage, or property damage arising out of your use of the Motorola Foundation Experiences in High Risk Activities. Foundation will not be responsible for the actions of any individual or any accident that results while using or attempting to use the Motorola Foundation Experiences. FAILURE OF THE MOTOROLA FOUNDATION EXPERIENCES DOES NOT CONSTITUTE AN OPPORTUNITY TO HOLD FOUNDATION LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES. YOU AND YOU ALONE ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR THE CONSEQUENCES OF USING THE MOTOROLA FOUNDATION EXPERIENCES. 7. Indemnity. You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold harmless Foundation and its affiliates, officers, agents, co-branders, partners, and employees from any third party claim or demand (including but not limited to damages, litigation costs, and reasonable attorney\'s fees) that relates to your use of the Motorola Foundation Experiences or your violation of this agreement. We reserve the right to assume the exclusive defense and control of any dispute in which you must indemnify us, and you agree to cooperate with our defense and settlement of these claims. We will use reasonable efforts to notify you of any such disputes once we become aware of them. 8. Term and Termination. You may use the Motorola Foundation Experiences licensed to you so long as you do not violate these terms of use or any applicable law. We reserve the right to: (1) limit or terminate your right to use the Motorola Foundation Experiences licensed to you at any time, and for any reason; (2) terminate any part of the Motorola Foundation Experiences licensed to you if we determine in good faith concern that such use violates an applicable law or these terms of use; and (3) inform law enforcement of any illegal activity or material relating to use of the Motorola Foundation Experiences and provide law enforcement officials with all requested information we may have, including but not limited to the name, phone number, and email addresses of any user account suspected of illegal activity. 9. Trademarks. Motorola Mobility Foundation and the Stylized M Logo are registered trademarks of Motorola Trademark Holdings, LLC. All other product or service names are the property of their respective owners. You may not alter, obscure, or render unclear any trademark, logo, or other notice that indicates the rights of Foundation or our licensors and suppliers, whether built into the Motorola Foundation Experiences, printed on packaging or promotional material, published online, or otherwise. 10. Notices. We may be required by state or federal law to notify you of certain events. In addition, we may need to notify you from time to time regarding changes to this agreement or the Motorola Foundation Experiences. Such notices will be effective upon our posting them to our website, your installation or use of any updates to the Motorola Foundation Experiences, or our delivery of a notice to you by email, postal mail, or other means as required by law. If you do not provide us with accurate information to contact you, we will not be held liable if we fail to notify you. You consent to receiving any notices regarding the the agreement or any notice required by law, including notice of a breach of security involving your personally identifiable information, through an email message or other electronic communication. Any notices that we send to you by email will be sent to the email address you provided when you registered for an account or any email address in your profile. 11. General information. This agreement supersedes any prior agreements between you and Foundation relating to your use of the Motorola Foundation Experiences. By using the Motorola Foundation Experiences, you agree that the statutes and laws of the United States and the State of Illinois, without regard to any principles of conflicts of law, will apply to all matters relating to your use of the Motorola Foundation Experiences. You also agree that any litigation will be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the state courts of Lake County, Illinois and the federal courts located in the Northern District of Illinois. You consent to the personal jurisdiction of those courts. Our failure to exercise or enforce any right or provision of this agreement does not waive our right to exercise or enforce our rights in the future. If any court finds a provision of these terms and conditions or the Motorola Foundation Experiences privacy policy to be invalid, then you agree that the court should endeavor to give effect to the intentions as reflected in the provision, and that the other provisions of this agreement will remain in full force and effect. These terms and conditions are subject to change without notice. Effective date: March 27, 2014</string>

</resources>
